tigerwoods.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy - Tiger Woods

### PRIVACY POLICY

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THIS “PRIVACY POLICY”) CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OUR WEBSITE OR ANY OTHER ETW CORP. PRODUCT OR SERVICE.

ETW Corp. is the organization that produces and publishes the official _websites for TGR, Tiger Woods Ventures and each of its verticals (TGR Live, TGR Design, Tiger Woods Foundation, The Woods Jupiter)_ (this or our “Website”). This Privacy Policy is applicable to these Websites and describes what information we collect, how we may use that information and the choices we offer for you to manage the information we collect related to your use of this Website.

  1. _Personal Information Collected Via This Website_
  2. _How We Use and Share Your Personal Information_
  3. _Other Information Collected And Shared Within This Website_
  4. _Other Circumstances When Your Data May Be Shared_
  5. _Managing Your Information_
  6. _Other Information_

  1. **Personal Information Collected Via This Website**

Information You Provide. You may visit and enjoy many elements of our Websites without disclosing any personal information about yourself. However, to make use of select, special, or enhanced elements of these Websites, you will need to share with us certain personal information so those elements may function properly. When you use certain enhanced elements within our Websites (e.g., create a profile, sign for the newsletter, or publish a comment), the personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to:

  * Full name,
  * Email address,
  * Password,
  * Street address,
  * Telephone number(s),
  * Birth date,
  * Payment card information,
  * Location data,
  * Contacts (as stored in your wireless device),
  * Other personal data, as detailed in this Privacy Policy, and data that may be requested from and provided by you.

If we collect such information, in most instances, the applicable page(s) or location(s) within these Websites will include statements regarding what information is required for the elements of these Websites to function properly and functionality for you to submit the requested or required information. In addition to the above list, there may also be opportunities for you to grant permission for use of other of your information in a manner set forth on the applicable page(s) within these Websites.

  2. **How We Use and Share Your Personal Information**

If you submit personal information to us, or to any third party acting on our behalf, we may use and share your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and as disclosed when you first submit your information. We will not sell, lease, publish, or share your personal information with or to anyone else, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may use and share your personal information as described in Section 1 above and we may:

  * Use your information to provide services you’ve requested or provide you with offers, promotions (e.g., a sweepstakes, fantasy game, subscription to goods or services) or content or add you to our postal mail list;

  * Share your information with certain third parties, including service providers, sponsors, and promotional partners, so they may help us provide services, offers, promotions, or content you’ve requested or otherwise in accordance with the applicable rules of a promotion or terms presented at the time you submit personal information, so the third party can administer the promotion, send you offers or content, or add you to their postal mailing list;

  * Share your information upon notice posted on an applicable location of these Websites where we collect your personal information for an economic transaction and notify you that we will be sharing such information with a third party; **or**
  * Use and share your information with permission from you.

  3. **Other Information Collected And Shared Within These Websites.**

  * Our Cookies and Web Beacons

We use and permit automatic methods such as cookies (small amounts of data which include a unique string of characters sent to your browser or application from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s or device’s hard drive), web beacons (technology used to track activity, also known as pixel tags) or similar technologies, alone or in combination with personally identifiable information you choose to provide us. Examples of the information we collect and analyze using such methods include, but is not limited to: personal information as authorized by you, the Internet protocol address used to connect your computer or device to the Internet; email address; login name and password; operating system type, version and computer or device platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locator clickstream to, on and from this Website, including date and time; and products you viewed or searched. We use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from a page. We use and may allow certain third parties, such as those who provide services associated with these Websites, to access these automatic data collection methods to enable you to use a “shopping cart” while using these Websites, to store your preferences and to improve, deliver, and customize these Websites’ content and offerings.

  * Third-Party Cookies and Web Beacons; Network Advertisers

We allow select third parties, such as those who deliver advertisements, content, social networking, or provide other services associated with this Website, to set cookies, web beacons or similar technologies in certain locations within these Websites or certain emails sent by us. Third-party companies that manage and deliver advertisements to websites and applications such as ours are commonly referred to as “network advertisers.” A permitted network advertiser may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to collect information about your interaction with these Websites in order to tailor certain advertisements and content delivered within these Websites and on other websites within such network advertiser’s ad network. You may elect to opt out of targeted behavioral advertising from many major third-party network advertisers by clicking here. If you would like to obtain more information about common industry practices of network advertisers or make choices about their use of your information or find additional opt-out tools operated by advertising industry associations encompassing even more network advertisers, please click here.

  * Social Networking

When using these Websites or when using certain third-party social networking services (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, Google+) (each and collectively, a “Social Network”), you may have the option to connect your Website information and activity with your Social Network information and activity. If you authorize such a connection, you permit us to share or publish information about your activity on these Websites with that Social Network and its users, and to access certain of your Social Network information, as disclosed by you at the time you consent to the connection. Information we may share with a Social Network may include, but is not limited to: technical information about your Website activity, your Website comments or the videos you watch on these Websites. Information we may access about you, with your consent, from a Social Network may include, but is not limited to, your basic Social Network information, your location data, your list of contacts, friends or followers, and certain of your activities on the Social Network. If you permit a connection between a Social Network and these Websites, we (and that Social Network) may be able to identify you and to associate information received pursuant to the connection with information we already have about you. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policy and privacy control options of any Social Network with which you choose to share information or connect to these Websites.

  4. **Other Circumstances When Your Data May Be Shared**

  * _Aggregated Demographic Information._

We may share aggregated demographic information with third parties. This information is not linked to personal information that can identify you or another individual person.

  * _Business Transfers._

As time passes, ETW Corp. and/or TGR, a Tiger Woods Venture may be sold along with its assets, or other corporate transactions may occur. In such a case, our customer information may be one of the business assets we transfer.

  * _Disclosure for Legal Purposes._

We may be required to share your personal and non-personal information pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants, or orders. If we are required to do so, we will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to use, disclose, or share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of Terms of Use of this Website or as required by law.

  5. **Managing Your Information**

You may choose and control what information you provide about yourself and certain information which is automatically collected via these Websites. If you do not wish to provide certain information necessary for enhanced functionality or content on these Websites, please do not use such functionality or content. If you have registered for an account through these Websites, you may review and revise certain of your account information by clicking here to log in, and then navigating the left-hand menu options. You may modify your subscriptions to our various promotional email communications and newsletters by accessing the “Newsletter Preferences” section within your Website account.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows a user to accept or reject most cookies. Certain cookies that are set when some video products are accessed on our Websites, called local shared objects or Flash cookies, may not be managed using the settings in your web browser. Information on managing, accepting, and rejecting these cookies is available from Adobe on the Adobe website. If you set your browser or Adobe Flash options not to accept cookies or local shared objects, you may not be able to take advantage of certain elements of this Website.

If you want to review or revise the personal information you provided during registration or in connection with a purchase or other activity while using these Websites, or close your Website account and have us delete the personal information in it (except for information that we keep for record-keeping purposes), you should contact TigerWoods.com Customer Service at info@tgr.ventures.

Remember that when you share information publicly online, it may be indexable by search engines or recorded by others, and any search engine index or record of your information may persist after you delete the information at the original source.

  6. **Other Information**

  * _No Spyware or Adware._

We do not install any spyware or adware in connection with these Websites, or distribute any commercial message, or authorize any third party to distribute any commercial message, by means of spyware or adware. “Spyware” or “adware” is any software which has been downloaded to or installed on an Internet user’s computer or device, without the user’s actual consent, and facilitates the distribution of any commercial message to the user. If you feel you may have spyware from another company installed on your machine, there are various anti-spyware/adware software applications available on the Internet to identify if this has occurred.

  * _Our Security Practices._

The account information associated with these Websites is password protected for your privacy and security. You choose your password for any of our Services so the strength of that password is determined by you. We recommend that you choose a unique password and not share your password with anyone else. In certain areas, we use industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

  * _Links._

These Websites contain links to other websites and products produced by TGR, Tiger Woods Ventures and to websites and products operated by unrelated third parties. In addition, if you click on an advertisement within these Websites, you may be directed to a web page within these Websites or to a third party website or product. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third-party websites or products, and we encourage you to read the privacy policies of every website and product that collects personally identifiable information from you. This Privacy Policy applies only to these Websites, unless you are notified otherwise upon accessing any third party website or product, in which case the terms and conditions set forth in such notification will apply.

  * _Your California Privacy Rights._

If you are a resident of California, pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, you may request information regarding our disclosure of your personal information to a third party for that party’s direct marketing purposes. Any such disclosure made to a third party by us would be otherwise in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

  * _Special Rules For Children._

Because of federal law, we are not permitted to knowingly collect any personal information from a child under the age of thirteen without the consent of that child’s parent or guardian. The statements in this Privacy Policy about our collection and use of personal information also apply to our treatment of personal information from children under the age of thirteen. Some elements of these Websites require the submission of a payment card number along with personal information in connection with a purchase; other elements of these Websites require the submission of personal information to access or use these Websites. Except in certain cases where limited contact information may be collected and not retained, these elements of these Websites are available to children under the age of thirteen. If a child who we know to be under the age of thirteen and for whom we have not received parental consent attempts to utilize a service on this Website which is not available to children, he/she will not be able to access it and may receive a message which relays that he/she is not eligible for such feature.

  * _Contact Us Regarding Privacy._

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: info@tgr.ventures.

  * _Notification of Changes._

If we make an important change to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notification and link on this Website’s homepage so that you may review the updated policy.
